A Guide to the Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 2 FA1440
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Indonesia and Southeast Asia, 1965-1982; 6; 5.97 Cubic Feet 12 letter document boxes and 3 legal document boxes
  - Natural Resource Management Seminar, Kuala Lumpur, 1979 June (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - Rural Labor Markets, Hyderabad, India, 1979 August 22-24 (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - Workshop on Village Studies, Los Banos, Philippines, 1979 July 16-19 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - Workshop on Rural Development and Fertility Behavior with Population Council (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - Philippine Biweekly Seminar Series (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - Farm Management Teaching Materials, 1978 May-June (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - Evaluation Research Seminar, Philippines (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - Economics Training in Southeast Asia (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - Coastal Zone Management Seminar, 1978 December (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - Diponegoro University - Brackish Water Fish Pond Management in Central Java (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - Agro-Economic Survey - Influence of Agri. Intensification on Social-Economic Life of Farm Families (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - School Dropouts and Their Impact on Agricultural Development in Sri Lanka (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - Chiangmai University - The Rural Organization Prospects for Increased Crop Production: A Case Study in Northern Thailand (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - Institutional Arrangements in Agricultural Organization (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - Economic Analysis of Alternative Strategies for Irrigation Development in Malaysia (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - Socioeconomic Study of Livestock Sector in Punjabi Villages, Pakistan (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Research on Indirect Impact of Pampanga River Irrigation Project (Box 118, Folder 2)
  - Analysis of Water Management Practices in East Java (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Resource Allocation of Transmigration and Local People in North Lusu, Abdul Karim Saleh (Box 118, Folder 4)
  - Brackish Water Pond Operators and New Technology (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Sociology of Development Workshop, Singapore, 1982 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - ASEA Meeting, 1979 November 27-29 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Research Methods Publications, 1976 (Box 118, Folder 8)
  - John Wong (Box 118, Folder 9)
  - Agricultural Innovation - Risk and Uncertainty in Sri Lanka (Box 118, Folder 10)
  - Modernization of Rural Society in Burma - Khin Maung Khi (Box 118, Folder 11)
  - Nek Buzdar Thesis Research (Box 118, Folder 12)
  - Comparison of Rice Production, 1930 and 1980 - Negeri Jemper University, RRTP (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - H. M. G. Herath - Resource Allocation by Rice Farmers in Sri Lanka (Box 118, Folder 14)
  - Laguna Resurvey (Box 118, Folder 15)
  - Satya Wacana University - On the Job Training Program in the Rural Social Sciences (Box 118, Folder 16)
  - Field Research with Rural Women in Bangladesh, Shamima Islam - Women for Women (Box 118, Folder 17)
  - Structural Context of Rural Poverty - The Case Western Visayas, Philippines (Box 118, Folder 18)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - L. Sondakh (Box 118, Folder 19)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Visiting Research Fellows (Box 118, Folder 20)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Mohammed Nazir (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Djamaluddin (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Johannes Palte (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Research Fellows Preliminary Discussions (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Supplements to Colombo Plan Fellowships in Australia (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - M. Ginting (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Consultants (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Rural Social Sciences in Indonesia (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - K. Nehen (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Faisal Kasryno (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Johannes Mandagi (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Dr. O. R. Krishnaswami Visit Research Consultant (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Research and Training (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Anwar Hafid (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Virginia Tomasek (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - 1974 SPRSS Projects (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Graduate Assistants (RSSP) (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - S. B. Simandjuntak (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Amin Aziz, 6.1.04, Graduate Assistant, UPCA (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Teaching and Research Materials (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Amundi Pasaribu, SPRSS Visiting Professor (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Yayasan (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Ford Foundation, 1972-1974 (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Ford Foundation, 1974-1976 (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Ford Foundation Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Ford Foundation Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Rural Social Sciences, 1972-1975 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Supplemental Program in Rural Social Sciences (SPRSS) - Advisory Committee Meetings, 1973-1975 (Box 123, Folder 2)
- USAID Funded Mechanization Project, 1977-1981; 7; 1.61 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes and 1 legal box
  - ADC-IRRI Mechanization Workshop, 1981 September 14-18 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - Studies and Papers, 1979-1980 (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
  - India Mechanization Grant - V. Abraham (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Indonesia Mechanization Project - Hurun (80-108-18), 1980 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Indonesia Mechanization Project - Tjahjadi Sugianto (80-101-19), 1980 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Sultoni Arifin Mechanization Grant (80-101-20), 1980 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Indonesia Project -Dwaswir Zein (81-101-21), 1981 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Nepal Mechanization Project (79-101-13), 1979 (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Paitoon Mechanization Project (79-101-14), 1979 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Bangladesh Mechanization Project - Alam (80-101-15), 1980 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Bangladesh Mechanization Project - Jasim (80-101-16), 1980 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Bangladesh Mechanization Project - Jabbar (79-101-06), 1979 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Indonseia-IRRI Mechanization Projects (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Pakistan Mechanization Project (78-101-01), 1978 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Malaysia Mechanization Project (78-101-02), 1978 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Indonesia Mechanization Project (78-101-03), 1978 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - India Mechanization Project (78-101-04), 1978 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Thailand Mechanization Project (79-101-05), 1979 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - AID Mechanization - Grant Proposal (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Mechanization Grants Pending (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - AID Mechanization - Early Correspondence, 1977 (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - Translations of Mechanization Papers (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - AID Mechanization - Proposals and Reports (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - AID Mechanization - Correspondence (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - AID Mechanization - Grant Award Statement (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - AID Mechanization - Reports to AID (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - AID Mechanization Grant - Administrative Documents (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - Reports and Papers, 1978-1980 (Box 126, Folder 5)
- Regional Research and Training Program (RRTP), 1970-1982; 8; 2.35 Cubic Feet 5 legal document boxes
  - Regional Research and Training Program (RRTP) - Reports, 1971-1980 (Box 127, Folder 1-4)
  - 1970-1973 International Development Research Center (IDRC) - Adminstrative records and Finance (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - 1974-1975 International Development Research Center (IDRC) (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - International Development Research Center (IDRC) 1980 Grant Letter (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - International Development Research Center (IDRC) 1980 Grant Request (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - International Development Research Center (IDRC) 1979 Grant Letter (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - International Development Research Center (IDRC) 1978 Grant Letter and Reports (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - International Development Research Center (IDRC) 1978 Grant Review (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - International Development Research Center (IDRC) 1978-1982 Grant Request (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - 1975-1977 Regional Research and Training Program Seminars and Workshops (Box 129, Folder 2-4)
  - 1970 Bangkok Conference on Graduate Education in Social Sciences in Asia (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Keizo Tsuchiya (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Regional Research and Training Program (RRTP) - Journal Subscriptions (Box 130, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Visiting Professors (Box 130, Folder 4)
  - L. S. Venkataramanan, 1977-1978 (Box 130, Folder 5)
  - 1971-1976 Regional Research and Training Program (RRTP) Correspondence (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - M. Halim Khah (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Sun Yik-Ching (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - International Development Research Center (IDRC) Grant 1976-1977 (Box 131, Folder 4)
- Field Office Staff Reports and Papers, 1954-1982; 9; 6.08 Cubic Feet 16 letter document boxes
  - Allee - Bicol Reports, 1960s (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Allee - Indonesia Reports, 1966-1968 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Barnett - Reports, 1962-1971 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Brown - Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Borton - Reports, 1960-1973 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - J. L. Buck and A. B. Lewis - Trip Notes, 1956 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Buck - Reports, 1954-1959 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Burger - Reports, 1977-1982 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Duewel - Reports, 1974 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Fort - Reports, 1961 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Gittinger - Reports, 1963-1965 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Hrabouszky - Reports, 1963-1965 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Kearl - Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Lampe - Reports, 1975 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Langham - Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Lewis - Trip Notes, 1956 October-December (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Lewis - Taiwan Reports, 1965-1967 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Mosher - Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Penny - Reports (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Bateson - General, 1976-1979 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Beers - General, 1961-1965 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Binswanger - General, 1974-1980 (Box 140, Folder 1-2)
  - Edward J. Clay - Reports and Papers (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - A. T. Mosher - Reports (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Ong - Reports, 1970-1977 (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Carl Pray - Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Retziaff and Roumasset - Reports, 1974-1980 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - V. W. Ruttan - Trip Reports, 1973-1977 (Box 143, Folder 3-4)
  - D. C. Taylor - Reports, 1969-1980 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - A. M. Weisblat - Reports, 1960-1975 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - C. R. Wharton - Reports, 1950s-1960s (Box 145, Folder 1-2)
  - Ben White - Reports, 1974-1977 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Collier - Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Collier - Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Plath - Reports, 1957-1959 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Provinse - Reports, 1957-1962 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Collier - Reports, 1970-1978 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Schickele - Reports, 1967-1972 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Southworth - Reports, 1967-1968 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - S. Lee Travers - China Report, 1981 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Evenson - Reports, 1974-1977 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Peterson - Reports, 1960-1962 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Sarle - Reports, 1962 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Sitton - Reports, 1959-1963 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Stevens - Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Strout - Reports, 1970-1975 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Stevenson - Reports, 1969 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Oppenfeld - Reports, 1956-1963 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Swenson - Reports, 1973-1979 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Wagner - Reports, 1963-1971 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Ward - Reports, 1968-1970 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Waxler - Reports, 1977-1980 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Weaver - Reports, 1968-1970 (Box 151, Folder 5)
- Staff Conference Files, 1972-1980; 10; 1.14 Cubic Feet 3 letter document boxes
  - Staff Conferences 1972 - Singapore (Box 151, Folder 6)
  - Staff Conferences 1973 - Chiangmai (Box 151, Folder 7)
  - Staff Conferences 1974 - Penang (Box 151, Folder 8)
  - Staff Conferences 1975 - Sri Lanka (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Staff Conferences 1976 - Indonesia (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Staff Conferences 1977 - Singapore (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - Staff Conferences 1978 - Bangkok (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Bangkok Staff Meeting, 1979 November 22-23 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Staff Conferences 1979 - Kuala Lumpur (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Staff Conferences 1980 - Srinagar, India, 1980 March 31-April 3 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Background papers, 1973-1979 (Box 153, Folder 2-3)
- Research and Training Network (RTN), 1971-1983; 11; 34.09 Cubic Feet 78 containers
  - Conference Papers - Resource Allocation and Productivity in International Agricultural Research, Virginia, 1975 January 26-29 (Box 154, Folder 1-4)
  - Conference Papers - Resource Allocation and Productivity in International Agricultural Research, Virginia, 1975 January 26-29 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Conference Papers - Problems on Field Data Collection on Social and Economic Issues in Rural Areas in the Middle East and Lebanon, Beirut, Lebanon, 1974 December 8-14 (Box 155, Folder 2-4)
  - Conference Papers - Minimum Information Systems for Agricultural Development in Low Income Countries, Oxford, England, 1976 December 6-9 (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Conference Papers - Workshop on Livestock Smallholder and Small Pastoralists, Winrock International Center, 1976 June 14-17 (Box 156, Folder 1-2)
  - Conference Papers - Group Farming Conference, Madison, WI, 1975 June 10-12 (Box 156, Folder 3-4)
  - Conference Papers - Group Farming Conference, Madison, WI, 1975 June 10-12 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Conference Papers - ADC-CIMMYT Risk and Uncertainty Conference, 1976 March 9-13 (Box 157, Folder 2-4)
  - Prospects for Growth, Princeton, NJ, 1974 December 1-4 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Seminar on Marketing Institutions and Services for Developing Agriculture, 1974 September 10-12 (Box 158, Folder 2)
  - Farm Management Teaching Workshop - Dr. Shao-er Ong, Kellog Center, East Lansing, MI, 1977 April 14-15 (Box 159, Folder 1-2)
  - Group Farming Systems, Madison, WI, 1975 June 10-12 (Box 159, Folder 3)
  - APO Conference, Tokyo, Japan, 1974 November 26-December 2 (Box 160, Folder 1-2)
  - Rural Marketing, Washington, D. C., 1974 January 3-4 (Box 160, Folder 3)
  - Survey Data Collection Planning Group, Singapore, 1974 January 12-13 (Box 160, Folder 4)
  - Rural Marketing, 1974 February 5 (Box 160, Folder 5)
  - AAEA Review of U. S. Training for Graduate Students, University of Wisconsin, Madison, WI, 1974 March 28-30 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Production Incentives Review Session, Columbus, OH, 1974 April 5-6 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - AAEA Review of U. S. Training for Graduate Students, 1974 February; March; April (Box 161, Folder 3)
  - AAEA Review of U. S. Training for Graduate Students, Washington, D. C., 1974 April 18-20 (Box 161, Folder 4)
  - Fertilizer, Nassau Inn, Princeton, NJ, 1974 May 23-25 (Box 162, Folder 1-2)
  - AAEA Review of International Training, International Committee, O'Hare Airport, IL, 1974 December 6 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Problems of Field Data Collection on Social and Economic Issues in Rural Areas in the Middle East and Africa, Beirut, Lebanon, 1974 December 8-14 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - AAEA Review of U. S. Training for Graduate Students, Palo Alto, CA, 1974 Feburary 14-16 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Cooperative Meeting (Latin American Experience), Bogota, Colombia, 1977 March 31-April 1 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Cooperative Meeting (Asian Experience), Philippines, 1977 April 4-5 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Sector Analysis Training Needs in Asia, Madison, WI, 1975 June 13 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Planning Committee Meeting on Sector Analysis, Boston, University, 1976 May 17 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Rural Development, 1975 May 23 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Growth, Productivity and Equality Issues in Brazilian Agriculture, Ohio State University, 1975 January 13-15 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Cooperatives, Small Farmers, and Rural Development, Madison, WI, 1977 June 23 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Cooperatives Meeting (African Experience), Nairobi, Kenya, 1977 May 9-10 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Les Small, Rutgers University, ARS and AMW, 1977 April 28 (Box 165, Folder 4)
  - Cooperatives, 1977 May 25 (Box 165, Folder 5)
  - Research on Irrigation, ADC, NY, 1977 May 23 (Box 165, Folder 6)
  - Cooperatives, Small Farmers and Rural Development, Racine, WI (Wingspread), 1978 April 24-26 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Review of V. W. Ruttan Book on Induced Innovation, 1975 January 20 (Box 166, Folder 2)
  - Group Farming Systems, Madison, WI, 1975 June 10-12 (Box 167, Folder 1)
  - Role of U.S. Cooperatives - the Small Farmer, Ford Foundation, NY, 1976 January 23 (Box 167, Folder 2)
  - Technology and Factor Markets, Singapore, 1976 August 7-9 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - Sector Analysis, Singapore, 1976 November 8-11 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - Resource Allocation and Productivity in International Agricultural Research, Arlie House, VA, 1975 January 26-29 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Household Studies, Sinapore, 1976 August 3-7 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Risk and Uncertainty in Agricultural Development, CIMMYT, 1976 March 9-13 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - Task Force in "Rural Economy", New Hampshire, 1977 January 13-15 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - Teaching Agricultural and Rural Development Administration, Cornell University, 1977 March 17-19 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - Small Farmers, Cooperatives and Development, Columbus, OH, 1977 January 19 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Farm Management Teaching, Kellogg Center, East Lansing, MI, 1977 April 14-15 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Nutrition Policy, 1973 November 12-14 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Cooperation, Small Farmers, and Development, Madison, WI, 1976 December 18 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Small Farmers, Cooperatives and Development, Washington, D. C., 1977 January 6 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Small Farmers, Cooperatives and Development, Washington, D. C., 1977 January 4 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Small Farmers, Cooperatives and Development, Washington, D. C., 1977 January 5 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Small Farmers, Cooperatives and Development, Washington, D. C., 1977 January (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Linkage of Agriculture and Education, India, 1977 January 6-9 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - International Communication of Information Based on Agricultural Research, CIMMYT, Mexico, 1978 June 15-16 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Minimum Information Systems for Agricultural Development in Low Income Countries, Oxford, England, 1976 December 6-9 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - Political Economy of Development, University of Minnesota, 1978 May 4 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - Small Farmers Marketing, Michigan State University, 1974 June 6-7 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - AAEA Report - Review of U. S. Training for Graduate Students, College Station, TX, 1974 August 18-21 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Participation of Women - Meeting to Set Agenda and Finalize Participant List, 1974 October 15 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Problems of Irrigation and Water Management in the Developing Countries, 1974 October 15-16 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Marketing Institutions and Services for Developing Agriculture, Washington, D. C., 1974 September 10-12 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Baviskar, Babue Rao, 1976 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Problems of Field Data Collection on Social and Economic Issues in Rural Areas in Asia, Singapore, 1974 October 27-November 2 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Problems of Field Data Collection on Social and Economic Issues in Rural Areas in Asia, Singapore, 1974 October 27-November 2 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Problems of Field Data Collection on Social and Economic Issues in Rural Areas in Latin America, CIMMYT, Mexico, 1974 November 17-23 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Research Resource Allocation, CIAT, Cali, Colombia, 1974 November 26-29 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - AAEA Review of International Training, O'Hare Airport, Chicago, 1974 October 21 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Cooperative Meeting - Asian Experiences Workshop - Country Reports, 1977 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Ladejinsky Seminar Planning Session, Washington, D. C., 1976 June 7 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Smallholder Livestock Production, Winrock, AR, 1976 June 13-17 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Management of Irrigation Systems in Southeast Asia, IRRI, 1976 June 22-25 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Role of the U. S. Cooperatives, The Small Farmer and Rural Development II, Madison, WI, 1976 July 16 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - Agricultural Land Reform and ITS Relationship to Development Research Needs in the 1970s (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Experience and Potential for Group Farming in Asia, 1977 August (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Cooperative Meeting (European Experience), London, 1977 May 5-6 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Rural Finance Research, San Diego, CA, 1977 July 28-August 2 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - AAEA International Committee Symposium, San Diego, CA, 1977 July 31-August 4 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Sector Analysis, Philippines, 1977 November 6-9 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Nutrition, Penn State University, 1977 October 3-4 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Cooperatives, Madison, WI, 1977 October 31-November 2 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Cooperatives, Washington, D. C., NRECA, 1977 November 17 (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Marine Resources Education, University of Rhode Island, 1977 November 30-December 2 (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Rural Development, Cambridge, MA, 1977 December 9-10 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Alan Strout - Rural Development - Exploratory Group Meeting, MIT (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Cooperatives - Planning Session, NY, 1978 January 13 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Production and Social Scientists Planning Session, NY, 1978 January 25 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - U. S. Training, NY, 1977 December 29 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Research Methodology in Study of Irrigation, Ft. Collins, CO, 1978 May 3 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - ADC Donor's Meeting, 1975 July 14 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Administration - AID-CSD - 2813 - Land Tenure Center Subcontract (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Administration - AID-CSD - 2813 - General Correspondence (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - RTN Committee Meeting, 1978 November 16 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Administration - Annual Report - Pending (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Administration - RTN Administrative Assistant (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Administration - AID-CSD - 2813 - Special Requests (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Administration - RTN Small Grants Program (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - RTN Program Committee Meetings, 1975-1978 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Review of RTN Program, 1974 May 16 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Administration - RTN Program Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - AID Meeting on RTN Program, Washington, D. C., 1977 April 16 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - RTN Reviews, 1971; 1972; 1974 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Administration - AID-CSD - 2813 - Annual Report (Box 182, Folder 2)